(The Last Challenge)
- Nice to see you all. - It's nice to see you.
Gosh, Sung Hwan.
Are you the same old Sung Hwan we used to know?
- You look great. - How much weight did you lose?
I lost about 12kg if you want a specific number.
But I didn't lose weight by going on a diet.
- Okay. - How did you lose weight then?
Since I was in my 20s, I had this dream...
- about my bucket list. - Okay.
I failed twice in my 20s to check it off my bucket list.
- In your 20s? - Yes, in my 20s.
I wanted to give it another try before I hit 50.
- But if I fail again this time, - That's it?
I'd never try it again.
So I gave it my all...
to my last challenge in my 40s from the bottom of my heart.
You can watch to find out whether I failed or succeeded.
- Your energy level says it all. - Right.
- Right? - He sounds like he succeeded.
- It would be funny if he failed. - To see if I failed or succeeded...
- But you never know. - Okay.
He was also cheerful when he failed the license test.
You're right.
(Let's find out.)
(Ku Walks Across the Country)
"Ku Walks Across the Country." Oh, this is nice.
(Sung Hwan is sleeping like a log.)
(Current time, 6:05am)
It's 6:05am.
(Tossing and turning)
(What time is it?)
(Turning off the alarm)
(He wakes up even before dawn breaks.)
Gosh, this is killing me.
Oh, my legs. Goodness.
Gosh, my legs.
(He gets up while groaning in pain.)
My body aches.
- You've gotten so slim. - My goodness.
I've never seen you this thin.
My goodness.
(His legs are covered with relief patches.)
- Relief patches... - So far...
Look at my feet. They got so tanned.
I thought you were already wearing socks.
(Familiar clothes are hanging in an unfamiliar room.)
(Lying back down)
(Sung Hwan is struggling to move around.)
Gosh, my back.
I'm at the community center of Anmak 1-gu...
in Gimhae, South Gyeongsang Province.
- The community center? - The community center?
Right now, I'm walking across the country...
- from Seoul to Busan. - Walk across the country?
- Walk across the country? - I love this.
A lot of people have walking across the country...
on their bucket list.
Walking across the country...
is the most romantic challenge I can think of.
That's true.
I tried this 2 times when I was in my 20s.
(I tried this 2 times when I was in my 20s.)
Then I failed both times.
This is my last challenge.
(It was 2004.)
- What? - What's this?
- What? - My gosh.
Were you really in your 20s?
That was 2004.
- At first... - Who's this?
- What? - What?
(He was full of youth and motivation.)
I think I'll probably arrive in Sokcho sometime next week.
It's been two weeks. But I'm not feeling well.
It's no joke. I'm covered in blisters.
(His condition suddenly got worse.)
During my first try, I got plantar fasciitis.
So I failed.
I was able to walk to Sokcho, though.
Ever since then,
I always had this thought in the back of my mind...
that I would try it again someday.
Then...
my dog had been with me for 11 years.
Kkotbun...
Losing her out of the blue like that...
took a huge emotional toll on me, I guess.
Of course, it's understandable. She was like my daughter.
I wanted to...
break away from this sense of loss.
And walking was the method I chose to do that.
I bet that motivated you even more.
It was really helpful. I mean it.
I set out on my third challenge of walking...
from my home in Cheonho-dong...
to Gwangalli Beach in Busan.
- The distance was 446km. - Gosh, 446km.
That's running 11 full course marathons.
I'll walk across the country.
I'm starting my cross-country journey today.
- How old were you in the video? - No.
(How old were you in the video?)
I can't tell your age in the videos.
That was the first day of my journey.
It was your first day?
- He does look younger. - His first day.
(He does look younger.)
I'm not sure if I will fail or succeed.
But here I go.
My gosh, I'm nervous.
Let's go!
As for my condition on Day One,
my feet and knees are good so far.
Let's go!
- He looks good on his first day. - Let's go.
What a cool view.
(Even in rain...)
My gosh, when it rained...
- Right. - It was hailing too?
- Hail... - Gosh.
(To make things worse, even when his feet hurt...)
I'm going to turn 50 soon.
But I wanted to give it a try no matter what.
If you can't avoid it, have fun with it.
(While enjoying all kinds of hardships, )
(he walked a total of...)
I have...
- Yangsan. - only 20km left to Busan.
He walked 421km?
I'm really close to the end.
I might tear up. Seriously.
For the past 16 days, I walked 421km.
Today is my last day.
To reach Gwangalli in Busan from Gimhae,
I just need to walk 25km more.
- It's my big finale. - Gosh, 25km.
Then how many days did it take for you to finish?
I initially planned to finish the walk in 14 days.
I had to keep walking, so I wasn't feeling well.
I kept increasing the total distance because I got more ambitious.
So I ended up adding three more days.
It became an 18-day journey according to my plan.
- Eighteen days. - You can adjust the days, I guess.
Then you'll release about 18 episodes?
Not that long.
- This is... - The runner is getting competitive.
Right. He's getting competitive.
- Out of 18 days... - No.
- Those 18 days... - He's the icon...
- of challenges. - That's his thing.
My gosh. Don't say that.
- You're stealing his thing. - It's for everyone.
Hey, I won't do another challenge.
Don't forget my Fun Run.
- Just don't throw up. - Right.
- Don't throw up. - You keep bringing that up.
(Okay. I'll let you have it.)
Didn't you walk to Busan, MINHO?
- I went from Busan to Seoul. - Right?
- Did you walk? - Really?
- I rode my bicycle. - I see.
- Gosh, no. I rode my bicycle. - Okay.
- You know what? - What a relief.
Don't share that story today. Let him take all the spotlight.
- Right. He should. - Stop it.
- Okay. - I almost died.
My gosh, I'm tired.
A friend of mine introduced me to this place.
It's a community center...
- in Anmak. - The lodging?
I'm not feeling well.
(The long, tiring journey has weakened his body and mind.)
(He just has to keep pushing for one more day.)
He definitely...
- looks the worst I've ever seen. - Right. Because...
- Right. - It's harder toward the end.
Hold on. Let me check the weather.
My goodness.
Oh, my legs.
Gosh, today...
(Let's see.)
It said it would rain in the afternoon, so I got up early.
Gosh, it will rain all day.
Why did it have to rain on my last day? This is annoying.
(Why on my last day of all days?)
Hongga.
Hongga?
Wake up.
He must be his colleague.
It's raining outside.
(Groaning)
It's...
- He startled me. - What?
(What was that just now?)
I thought it was his dad.
- This isn't "The Roundup," right? - It's not.
He's not from the movies.
- He's my actual friend. - He's not?
It's not raining that hard for now. But it is still raining.
(His partner has an intense look.)
His name is Hong Yu Chang.
He's a rapper.
- And his stage name is Hongga. - He's a rapper?
- He's a rapper. - He's my senior rapper.
We've been friends for seven years.
He went on most trips with me and Kkotbun...
out of all my friends.
I bet he raps aggressively.
- No. He's really mellow. - Really?
Kkotbun probably spent the most time...
with him after Ju Seung.
He's like family.
- Was he... - It's raining outside.
- with you for the whole walk? - Yes, he was.
- Really? - You must be so grateful.
I told him I was leaving tomorrow to do this.
He told me it was on his bucket list...
and wanted to try it for a long time.
He asked me if he could join me.
I told him it was a big decision and he needed to be ready.
- Right. - Then we decided to do it together.
- He's so innocent. - He is.
I guess you're close to him too.
I thought Ju Seung would do it with him.
Ju Seung would be too fast because he'd just use shukuchi.
He could get there in four days.
Our pace would be different.
(You needed 17 days? I can do it in 4.)
(He checks on the laundry as soon as he gets up.)
Did you get some sleep?
My shoulders hurt.
(His walking partner folds the laundry first.)
(Grunting)
I felt like a soldier who fought in 100 battles.
It wasn't just localized pain. My whole body ached.
(Groaning)
Hey, today is our last day, by the way.
I guess we're nearing the end, after all.
But it's killing me.
- Gosh. - My goodness.
- That's cute. - His forehead got tanned.
His forehead...
- That's special effects makeup. - Is that makeup?
He has garaetteok on his forehead.
Doesn't it look like a halo?
- Ding. - The halo around angels.
He looks like a celestial rapper.
- Right. We walked for 16 days. - Yes.
- He wore a headband. - Yes.
He sweats a lot.
Wearing a hat for nine hours was uncomfortable for him.
- He applied a lot of sunscreen. - He did, right?
But he still got tanned like that.
(Their 16-day walk beat sunscreen.)
(He still finds it funny.)
We have to get ready fast. It's raining.
That must hurt.
My gosh.
Relief patches aren't working now.
Relief patches...
But you look super young.
He looks younger...
- than when he was in his 20s. - Sung Hwan.
(Limping)
(He tries to get ready quickly despite his tired body.)
(Getting up)
Let's tidy up this place.
(Hongga finishes tidying up his things before Sung Hwan.)
(Getting on the foam roller)
Look how tanned his thighs are.
- Gosh, that's crazy. - Oh, my.
(A clear tan line)
UV rays are no joke.
(Soon after, Sung Hwan also...)
This is the best.
(starts massaging his feet.)
(It hurts, but it feels good.)
- That must hurt. - It hurts, but it feels so good.
(Doing his best)
(After thoroughly massaging their muscles...)
How are your feet?
The blisters...
Once the old ones are gone, I get new ones. That repeats.
It's a blister.
(His toes are covered in blisters.)
Underneath...
(Oh, no.)
Doesn't it hurt?
- My feet didn't get blisters. - Underneath?
But his feet were covered in blisters.
My gosh. Oh, no.
I'm in charge of breakfast. So I'll cook.
Do you want your usual amount?
Okay. Sounds good.
Okay.
(Grabbing)
The SKJ...
Ramyeon.
(He fills the pot with water.)
It's on.
We had to eat carbs in the morning no matter what.
(Adding the noodles from jjajang ramyeon)
(Then he also adds noodles from kalguksu ramyeon...)
(and the squid-flavored ramyeon too.)
- What kind of combo is this? - That's it.
I call it SKJ.
It has squid-flavored ramyeon,
- Kalguksu. - the anchovy kalguksu ramyeon,
and jjajang ramyeon.
Together, I call it SKJ. It's really good.
(Cooking fried eggs to eat with the ramyeon)
(Meanwhile, Hongga...)
(sets up a place to eat without being told to do so.)
- That looks good. - I wonder how it tastes.
The noodles look nice and thick. I bet it tastes good.
That looks amazing. I'd love to try it.
All done. Let's eat.
It's called SKJ ramyeon.
Try the good, old SKJ ramyeon. It's been a while. Eat a lot.
(Loading up on noodles to save energy)
- The noodles got soggy. - We must eat them fast.
They didn't get too soggy. They're perfect.
Gosh, that looks really good.
- With the noodles... - It looks so good.
(I need some protein to get some strength for the day.)
I love having noodles like this for breakfast. It's so good.
- Like ramyeon at orientations. - You can taste the jjajang sauce...
and the seafood.
- You get the anchovy flavor too. - Gosh, that sounds so good.
- It must taste so good with kimchi. - Yes.
My gosh. This is crazy, right?
(Nodding)
(Slurping)
We haven't had it in a while. It tastes so good.
(We must eat up for energy.)
That was so good.
(Gobbling up the food to complete the journey)
- I know how much you eat. - Don't eat too much.
This is my last bite.
I'll keep on eating if there's food.
I'll get tired while walking later.
(You're right.)
- Wait. He has those baby eyes. - Yes.
- They resemble each other. - He has kind eyes.
- He has those pure baby eyes. - Yes.
- He looks like a baby too. - He resembles an infant.
- An infant? - Right.
- Remove the beard. And he's a baby. - He's a baby.
- Right. - He does look like a baby.
I'll clean up.
Take your time.
I'm done.
Can you remove the wooden chopsticks?
- Take care of the trash for me. - Okay.
(Sung Hwan washes the dishes.)
(Hongga cleans up.)
(The fantastic duo finishes in no time with their teamwork.)
(Checking his phone)
I need to get ready.
(Hongga is engrossed in something.)
(Checking their route for the day)
- It's the map. - We have different tasks...
in the morning.
I have no sense of direction and everyone knows it.
But Hongga has the best sense of direction.
That's why we divided up our responsibilities.
Hongga's role is finding the path like the GPS.
My role is coming up with the schedule...
and cooking.
That's how we split up our roles.
- Then you definitely needed him. - Yes.
(Sitting down)
Oh, right.
How much did we walk yesterday?
- Wait. Let me check. - Okay.
(The Walking GPS calculates it right away.)
We walked 24km yesterday.
- He... Yes. - He wrote everything down.
You need to record everything.
So,
with that,
we'll arrive here.
Give it to me. Gosh, this is the big day.
(Overwhelmed)
Is this our 16th day? Or the 17th day?
That's confusing.
- He's so thorough. - It's our 17th day.
Toward the end, your pace slowed down.
- It slowed down a lot. - Right, it did.
That's a really cool record.
It's our last day. It's D-Day.
(The day they will complete their long 17-day walking journey)
- We just have to walk 25km today. - We have to walk 25km today.
But we might have to walk 1km more.
- When we finish... - So 25km...
That gives us a total distance of 446km, right?
- Later... - Our initial goal was 425km.
- But we increased it by 20km. - Okay.
Do you know what I noticed...
when I rode my bicycle from Busan to Seoul?
I had to climb over a mountain while passing through...
North Gyeongsang Province. There was no way around it.
There was no other path.
When I was climbing, I thought,
"My gosh. This isn't right."
"I can't do this." I didn't think I could do it.
- But there was a downward path too. - Right.
- That boosted my energy then. - Right.
There's no shortcut while walking across the country.
Let's say you want to rest for one more hour.
- Then you must walk more later. - Right.
There's no homework. If it's an uphill path, you just walk.
If you put it off,
- it's harder the next day. Right. - I must walk more the next day.
It will be more tiring.
You got a life lesson.
(After checking the remaining distance...)
- We're set. - Okay.
(Getting ready one last time with determination)
(Grabbing)
(Taping their knees to complete the journey)
We have to tape our knees well.
It's an anti-inflammatory painkiller.
(Going into battle on painkillers)
- I can sense your determination. - Yes.
(Getting ready smoothly)
(Taking it out)
Help me put this on.
- What's that? - What is it?
She should...
walk with me today.
I had bought other things for Kkotbun. But she had always...
worn this leash since she was two months old.
- Kkotbun's leash. - It's Kkotbun's leash? Gosh.
I wore the leash on my wrist.
It helped me tremendously when it got really tough.
I would say, "Gosh, I'm so tired." Then I would look at it.
Strangely, it gave me a bit more energy.
That's the fascinating thing about dogs.
They give us a reason to keep living when they're alive.
But even when they're gone, they still push us to live.
- Right. - It was the same with me.
- That's really fascinating. - I see.
Even Kkotbun walked across the country.
(Kkotbun has been with him every step of the way.)
That's so cool.
- It's admirable. - Yes.
It's so admirable.
Let's go.
We can't come back later.
Luckily, it's not raining now. It stopped.
Let's stretch our shoulders and go.
(Stretching before they set out)
My gosh, my shoulders hurt so much. Wait, to the left.
If we don't stretch, our posture gets twisted.
All right. Let's...
- begin another day of walking. - Sung Hwan.
- If we say it's good, it's good. - It's good.
- If we say we can do it, we can. - We can.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Gosh, that's so cool.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(They set out at 8am.)
(The two of them are walking to their final destination.)
How do you feel?
I'm just...
Well,
let's try our best.
It might be because it's not raining yet this morning.
I feel great.
It's our last day too.
My gosh, this is great.
(Feeling great)
I'm always in a great mood when we start out.
- Yes. - Yes.
The beginning is always the best part.
I really hope I can continue with this energy level.
(Same here.)
(Fortunately, they feel great at the start of their last day.)
You felt lighter, though. Right?
It was our last day too.
And we were getting close to our destination.
I need to read the map accurately.
(Focused)
This way.
Go straight.
(Thanks to the Walking GPS, they keep walking without worry.)
(Looking reliable)
Gosh, we both love beer.
- You both like to drink. - I see.
We promised each other...
that we wouldn't have a drop of alcohol or overeat.
If we overeat,
- our pace will slow down. - Right.
We tried really hard to keep these two promises.
It's our last day.
What do you want to eat the most after this?
I want fried chicken...
- Me too. I craved that too. - with draft beer...
- and a shot of soju. - Gosh.
He's smiling.
(Giggling)
I also want tteokbokki and sundae.
(Visualizing)
This is like military training.
- It was quite similar to that. - Right.
- I did that too while marching. - Right.
It's just like military training.
I want...
Since we'll be in Busan...
Wait. CO KUN talked about this. What was that?
- What is it? - I really craved it.
Lee Jae Mo Pizza.
- I see. - Pizza.
A can of beer to go with that.
Okay. I love it. Pizza.
(Just thinking about food brings up his appetite.)
You know what? The weather forecast said...
it would rain a lot starting at 7am.
- Yes. - The weather is on our side.
- I hope it stays that way. - So... Yes.
Gosh. It's not raining, though.
The universe is on our side!
It didn't rain.
The forecast said it would rain a lot!
I knew it! The universe is on our side!
It's on our side!
I felt so good.
When you walk in the rain, your feet get wet.
Right.
Hey. We're full of energy in the morning.
- If we say it's good... - It's good!
- If we say we can do it, we can! - We can!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
You guys have excellent teamwork.
We had nothing to talk about.
- We did that for 17 days. - Really?
- Right. - Let's go.
This chant helped us a lot while walking.
- Right. Chants are important. - Yes, they are.
- They help you stay grounded. - Right.
So they're important.
(West Nakdong River)
(With their powerful chant they shouted for 17 days, )
(they cheerfully keep marching.)
Gosh, how beautiful.
Oh, my.
(A pink tunnel of cherry blossoms)
- What a nice path. - Gosh.
It's so beautiful.
This always gives me energy when I'm out walking.
When I'm about to get tired,
I see beautiful trails like this.
(Amazed)
This is the exact reason I wanted to walk across the country.
- What a beautiful place. - Yes.
(They walk while enjoying the floral scent.)
I love walking like this.
I mean, even now,
I'm not thinking about anything.
Right.
I have zero thoughts, which is nice.
When will I get a chance to enjoy a beautiful trail like this?
(When will I get a chance to enjoy a beautiful trail like this?)
Look over there. This entire place is beautiful.
(A moment with a breathtaking view including the Nakdong River)
It's definitely less exhausting when the view is nice.
It was so beautiful.
The trail we walked...
Out of all the trails we walked, today's trail...
was the longest one with cherry blossoms.
The cherry blossoms here haven't bloomed yet.
Wait, are they not cherry blossoms?
That was from Day One when we had just begun.
I see. On your first day...
The cherry blossoms hadn't bloomed yet.
Seriously. They look just like popcorn.
- Beautiful, right? - They bloomed gradually.
It gets warmer in the south.
- Flowers bloom early there. - Yes.
They look like popcorn.
(Filmed by Sung Hwan)
The cherry blossoms are welcoming us.
This is nice.
(The most romantic sight on their last day)
Gosh, this trail is just crazy.
This is such a luxury for us. I mean it.
My gosh. It's already become a cherished memory.
(Thanks to that, they're getting into the spring spirit.)
The petals are falling down.
(Getting showered by the petals, the peak of romance)
Seriously.
I'll never forget this moment until the day I die.
(Sung Hwan's journey across the country, filled with romance)
(Sighing)
Gosh, I'm feeling it now.
Forget about the romantic view or whatever. How far did we come?
Only 2km.
- You only walked 2km? - My gosh. Only that?
- Gosh, around that time... - Your energy level dropped so fast.
(His energy level dropped rapidly.)
It's only been 2km.
Our fatigue accumulated. That's why...
we get tired quickly.
It's because of ongoing fatigue, right?
He's been walking at his limit.
- Right. I was at my limit. - He had already hit his limit.
- I hit my limit three days ago. - Right?
(Community Center of Anmak 1-gu to Gwangalli Beach)
(Distance traveled: 2km)
We have a long way to go.
- Gosh. - That's long indeed.
(Glancing)
"Agricultural Technology Center."
(Entering Busan)
- But you guys made it to Busan. - It's Busan.
We slept in Gimhae the night before, and we made it to Busan.
- You guys are getting close. - Yes.
- Is that Gupo? Or the one after? - It's right here.
We'll have to cross it.
(Heading toward Gupo with the Walking GPS' guidance)
Gosh, we have to climb stairs again.
To cross the Gupo Bridge,
we have to climb up the stairs to cross it.
(Trying their best to climb the stairs)
Stairs are the toughest.
- Oh, my. - That's not easy.
- It wasn't easy. - Oh, my.
- If we say it's good, it's good. - It's good.
- If we say we can do it, we can. - We can.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Let's go.
- You can't do it without the chant. - Let's go.
- Oh, my knees. - They must bring up their energy.
Let's go.
I know you have bad knees. This is impressive.
Right. It's really hard to walk when your knees hurt.
(Sung Hwan keeps pushing himself despite the unfavorable conditions.)
Sung Hwan, your determination is impressive.
Right. This isn't easy.
- He's so determined. - You're amazing.
Let's go.
(They barely manage to climb up to the Gupo Bridge.)
(Zooming by)
(Swooshing)
(Swishing)
Gosh, it's super windy up here.
(On an elevated bridge...)
It was incredibly windy on the bridge.
I can't keep my eyes open.
The wind was typhoon-level strong.
(Walking for quite a while against the strong wind)
(Exclaiming)
(Frowning)
- Oh, gosh. - What is it?
(Sung Hwan's face twists more and more.)
(Fidgety)
- Oh, gosh. - What is it?
(Sung Hwan seems to feel uncomfortable...)
(on top of Gupo Bridge.)
(Fidgety)
- I need to use the restroom. - Okay.
- A gas station or... - Oh, his stomach hurts.
I need to... My gosh.
He ate too much.
(Was my breakfast too hearty?)
Gosh, there's no restroom...
on the cross-country track. This is driving me crazy.
(Quickly looking for the restroom)
- He's looking for the restroom. - This is serious.
There's a 911 rescue center.
- When we go down? - Yes, let's go there.
I think we're around 500m or 600m away.
(He'll use the restroom of the rescue center under the bridge.)
I might end up in big trouble.
Back then, I was...
Why is the bridge so long?
Gosh, I'm dying to poop.
(I'm dying to poop.)
You're so instinct-driven.
I had it really hard then.
My goodness.
(Halting)
Gosh, this is serious.
Goodness, what do I do?
It was really hard then. It was a crisis.
Gosh, there's no restroom on the cross-country track.
- This is driving me crazy. - There's no restroom.
Those who have done a cross-country walk must know.
Going to a restroom...
- is troublesome. - It must not be easy.
There are times when there aren't any convenience stores within 10km.
- What do you do then? - It's really hard to find one...
- once you're out of city. - You're right.
That must be the worst.
(Worried)
Do we have about 300m to go?
We have around 300m to go. We can go down this way.
It was really hard then.
(He's on the verge of crying.)
- Oh, gosh. - You should minimize moving.
That's right. You should shake your upper body less.
My gosh.
Gosh, this is really serious.
The poop is almost hanging.
What did he say?
Sung Hwan is walking while clenching his anus.
Seriously...
But your bow-legged walking is fixed.
(Thanks to that, his bow-legged walking is fixed.)
(His unrivaled bow-legged walking he's been keeping for a long time)
That's good.
Gosh, my stomach hurts.
He's almost there.
(He can slowly see the end of the bridge.)
(But hold on.)
It came out.
(The 2nd stomach issue)
How much longer to go?
It's right below. Let's go.
Gosh, I should get ready.
Open it.
That's right.
- You should get ready in advance. - Yes, it's important.
He should go as soon as he opens the door.
It's open.
Hongga, please take this in advance.
This won't do.
Hongga did so many things.
(Taking each step carefully)
It's tough when you go down.
(911 Rescue Center)
It really is an emergency.
(Finally, )
(Sung Hwan is rescued.)
Thank you. I almost died.
- I almost died. - You feel ecstatic then.
Thank you so much.
- Not at all. - You're my lifesaver.
- Thank you. I'm off. - Bye.
I'll drop by to say hello next time when I'm in town.
(I feel better now.)
He looks more relaxed.
- Hongga. - Yes?
Happiness is right beside you, not somewhere far.
This is something so small, but it makes me so happy.
He's learning about life.
I almost died.
It's full-on downtown from here.
(They reach the city center after crossing Gupo Bridge.)
Yes, from now...
I want to drink something cold.
Right.
For eight days, we only walked country roads.
It was our first time...
- seeing the city center. - Right.
You must've been glad to see the city.
Where are they?
(After walking through the alley, an overpass shows up.)
- It's an overpass. - Yes.
The overpass is...
As we walked, we realized...
there were so many overpasses in Korea.
(They start climbing up the stairs.)
Goodness.
(Sighing)
(He's exhausted as soon as he starts climbing.)
All right.
(Where did his bright smile from a moment ago go?)
(His smile disappeared in an instant.)
All right.
(Sighing)
Your knees must've been destroyed.
(He crossed the overpass with difficulty.)
(Breathing out)
(Soon, they start going uphill.)
(Sighing)
The apple we had last time...
- and strawberries. - Strawberries.
(As he's exhausted, he thinks of fruits.)
I suddenly crave those.
- They must be low on sugar. - Here...
(I crave something sweet.)
(The uphill road continues.)
Gosh, my legs.
My knees hurt too.
(Panting)
An uphill road is really tough.
- Hongga didn't say a word. - Turn right here.
He's amazing.
Gosh, my legs.
(He continues to go forward with Hongga who's been quiet.)
How are the tangerines so beautiful?
Gosh, this is no joke!
(It's a fruit store!)
My hands are shaking!
Thank you.
(Suddenly getting excited upon seeing fruits on the way)
Gosh, I'm so tired.
As soon as we talked about fruits,
we came into a fruit alley.
What is this? They're all fruit stores.
We just talked about fruits.
What kind of apple is this?
- I shouldn't look. - That's green apple.
- It's Korean beef. - You just walked past it?
- You could eat 1. - You could've eaten 1.
I was going to eat during a break.
- He had to eat during a break. - He planned out a routine.
It's more difficult in the city.
You didn't eat while walking.
Gosh, look at that.
Old-style jjajangmyeon. Machine-made milmyeon.
The sign that says Chinese food is all ripped.
(Fancy restaurants that tempt Sung Hwan)
I can smell Busan in the air.
Gosh, it's making me hungry.
He must be dying to have gukbap.
- You love snacking. - I love it.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hi.
Yes, hello.
- Gosh, ma'am. - Oh, my. You're thin.
I'm thinner than you thought, right?
You became thinner.
Right.
- Yes. - You're so handsome.
- My lady. - Your face is so thin.
Oh, my.
- How come your face is so thin? - It's her first time seeing him.
You're so thin.
- Your face is so thin. - Let's go.
Wait, ma'am! I'm sorry, but you look like me a little.
I've found my mom.
Mom!
- Mom! - Your smile resembles hers.
I'll get going.
- I'll get going. - All right. Have a good one.
- I won't go far to see you off. - Bye!
(Setting off after getting cheered on by the ladies...)
(instead of snacking)
It really cheered me on.
I got cheered on a lot,
- and it helped a lot. - Of course.
(So far, they've walked 8.5km.)
You've come quite far.
They've come a third of the way.
(Remaining distance: 16.5km)
(Going forward quietly)
Gosh, the rain...
Please don't rain.
(Rain slowly starts to fall.)
What's wrong with you?
Since I was wet anyway, I let myself get soaked comfortably.
(This is fun!)
(What's so fun about it?)
He must not talk much except when he raps.
It won't rain more than this.
It's a passing shower.
For a weather fairy like me,
this is all I get.
We can enjoy this much of rain.
(Boom)
(The sky suddenly turns wild.)
Oh, no.
- What bad timing. - As soon as I said that...
It's the same sound...
- from the 911 rescue center. - Exactly.
(Embarrassed)
Please don't be mad. I was just saying it.
(Calm down.)
(Calming down the enraged sky)
(The place they reached after walking for a while)
That's... Gosh, look how good it looks.
Fresh mango bingsu.
Bingsu?
(Fresh mango bingsu)
- When you're low on sugar... - Inhale it!
I'm a bit wet. I'm sorry.
(They enter the place to inhale bingsu.)
We have one snack time.
If the final destination of the day is 26km away...
and a cafe is located at a 15-km point,
we go to that cafe and rest for an hour.
Eating carbs makes us tired,
so we always eat a shake or bingsu.
We eat sugary treats our bodies can absorb.
There aren't many places where we can rest,
so we decide on...
what to eat the day before.
That makes sense. That could change the route.
I wrote that the day before.
- Is that the mango bingsu? - Yes.
I'll order one. I'll order this.
- I'll order patbingsu. - One fresh mango bingsu...
and one patbingsu?
(They go to the table after ordering bingsu.)
(His body aches.)
He struggles to sit.
My goodness.
(Dazed)
- Hold on. - Their eyes are unfocused.
It's like a mirror.
(It's like a mirror.)
How many kilometers have we traveled?
- We've traveled 11km. - Did you say 11km?
That means we have 14km left to go.
(The remaining distance is 14km.)
I'm so low on sugar.
(He feels dizzy.)
The bingsu you've ordered is ready.
(Finally!)
(Bingsu enters.)
Ma'am.
The bingsu you've ordered is ready.
Ma'am. Thank you.
Here.
- Let's share. - Shall we do that?
- That's insane. - We can scoop out some.
Okay.
- It looks tasty. - I prefer patbingsu.
It looks good.
Look at this mango.
(Appetizing)
(Gasping)
I usually don't like fruits.
(I usually don't like fruits.)
(I love fruits.)
Gosh, look at this. This makes me eat a lot of mangoes.
(Eating)
- His face lit up right away. - My goodness.
(His skin looked dull since he was low on sugar.)
His face suddenly lit up.
(His skin is glowing thanks to bingsu.)
It really raises my blood sugar.
It spread through my veins.
- How fascinating! - My goodness.
(Hongga quickly raises his blood sugar as well.)
- It looks like bibimbap. - I know.
Didn't your teeth feel cold?
They did, but I kept eating because it was so tasty.
He'll go to the 911 center again.
(Watch out for a stomachache.)
Any snack would've tasted good at that point, right?
(A snack break that's as good as a feast)
(His mouth waters.)
I can breathe more easily now.
(It washed away his fatigue.)
What are you going to do with that forehead?
- Didn't he apply sunscreen? - He did.
That day, the sun wasn't so bad because of the rain.
How will you function...
in society?
(Sighing)
(Let's see.)
(Staring)
I guess it's pretty bad.
Oh, no.
For now...
(Upset)
To be honest, I'm so exhausted and weary.
Even if we're tired... If we say it's good,
- it's good. - It's good.
If we say we can do it...
- We can. Let's go! - Let's go!
- They're a positive duo. - I know.
They don't even complain.
(Distance traveled: 11km Distance remaining: 14km)
Be careful.
They ate bingsu on a rainy day.
Hey, this route is strange.
Why?
A tunnel?
Busan has so many interesting paths.
Oh, my. How is there...
- What? - such a narrow tunnel?
- What's this? - What?
I would never go in there when I'm running.
(Looking around)
It's a cave.
That tunnel looks cool.
- It's like a mystery spot. - How fascinating.
Hongga should film a music video inside the tunnel.
He had the exact same thought.
- Right? - He wanted to do that next time.
Rappers lose it when they see a tunnel.
- Why do they lose it? - Really?
- They want to rap right away. - Do they want to do this?
Do rappers get excited when they see a tunnel?
When they see a cool tunnel, they think of a camera first.
All of the old music videos were filmed inside a tunnel.
- And that tunnel is unique. - Right.
He must have been excited walking there.
Is that rain?
It's raining hard.
(Rain has turned heavier.)
Gosh, even the weather is...
on our side.
You could slip in the rain.
Since it rained a lot, the road was very slippery.
Still, it's nice to do this on a rainy day.
Rain harder!
(Grimacing)
Hongga is more expressive than most actors.
- He doesn't even need to talk. - No.
He speaks with his face.
(I'm impressed.)
(They can barely open their eyes because of the rain.)
My goodness.
(But they keep walking toward the Gwangalli Beach.)
Even the weather helps our festival.
Gosh, it's scary.
(At the end of the fear-filled gaze)
- Is that it? - It's this way.
(An uphill road appears.)
I hate an uphill road.
Stairs are better.
(They meet an uphill road after walking about 430km.)
(Grunting)
(Hold on.)
This hill is intense.
What's that?
(He becomes speechless.)
Is there another one?
This isn't a hill, but a mountain.
Sung Hwan usually doesn't take...
- an uphill road. - I know.
So it'll be hard on his calves and glutes.
(Panting)
- The uphill continues. - It continues.
It's almost a mountain.
(Their feet become heavy.)
(He hangs his head.)
It's seriously steep.
(The boss-level uphill road appears.)
- Go on. I'll follow you. - Come on, Sung Hwan.
(Go on without me. I'll follow you.)
It's too much.
(The endless uphill road exhausts him.)
(Dizzying)
(My goodness)
At that moment...
Why did I decide to do the cross-country match?
The weather is insane.
Gosh, it's raining so hard.
It's doing that again. My knees don't move as I want.
Please save us.
Let's do it together!
(I Live Alone)
Let's welcome the guest of the Rainbow Live.
It's IRF,
Introducing the Rainbow Friends.
- Who is the friend? - Tell us.
It's my friend this time as well.
You have so many friends.
Let me give you a hint.
Every work my friend starred in became a hit.
"Escape from Mogadishu."
"1987: When the Day Comes."
"Guardian: The Lonely and Great God."
- I watched all three. - Who is it?
This is my second friend after In Hyuk.
It's Park Gyeong Hye.
- Welcome. - Welcome.
- Gyeong Hye. - Hello.
- Welcome. - Hello.
(She was a sweet and scary ghost...)
(in "Guardian: The Lonely and Great God.")
(She shines even when she is amidst the senior actors.)
("See You Tomorrow," "Hwayi: A Monster Boy," "Salut d'Amour,")
("Big Match," "Jane," "Bowling Bling," "1987: When the Day Comes,")
("Fabricated City," "The Drug King," "Maggie," "My Dream Class," etc.)
(The lovely scene stealer, Actress Park Gyeong Hye)
- Sung Hwan. - Gyeong Hye.
- You've lost so much weight. - Oh, my.
Sung Hwan.
Gyeong Hye, please say hello to the viewers.
Hello, I'm Actress Park Gyeong Hye.
I'm very, extremely nervous. Thank you.
(Welcome.)
How does it feel to be here?
(Hesitant)
I'm still a bit nervous.
How did the two of you become close?
We were in a movie together.
After that, we were in the same agency for 5 to 6 years.
We met when we played the villains...
and became close.
Her tone and performance were incredible.
- You wanted to recruit her. - She signed the contract...
the very next day.
Thanks to Sung Hwan, I entered the agency.
He looked after me when I was in the agency.
It's so fascinating to stand next to Gyeong Hye here.
Isn't it fascinating?
(She feels embarrassed.)
Let's check out the daily life of Park Gyeong Hye.
(The Power of Positivity)
Gyeong Hye is very cheerful.
(Sunlight enters the room through the curtains.)
There are no blackout curtains.
I realized that they didn't have the blackout function...
- after the purchase. - What?
- Really? - Yes.
Wouldn't you get tanned with so much sunlight?
I didn't think of that.
(She gets startled and wakes up at the sound of the alarm.)
(Feeling embarrassed)
(Getting up)
(She curls back in after turning off the alarm.)
(Gasping)
You're flexible.
Aren't my pants too high up?
- My pants! - It's fine. It looks natural.
(Fidgeting)
(She finally gets up.)
(Wilson greets her in the morning.)
(Fascinated)
Hello.
I'm Actress Park Gyeong Hye,
and I've lived alone for four months.
It hasn't been that long.
It's my first time living alone.
It was my first time finding my own house.
I live in Yeoksam-dong, Gangnam-gu.
It's around 19 square meters.
With a security deposit of 50,000 dollars,
the monthly rent is 590 dollars...
including maintenance and parking fees.
That's a very cheap deal.
- These days, - She found a good deal.
Studio apartments in Gangnam cost around 1,500 dollars a month.
(Hanger cover, extended hanger, clothes storage boxes)
(Her clothes are neatly stored in the small area.)
Gosh!
Gosh, that startled me.
- Gosh! - Socks need to be dried well.
- Gosh! - Right.
(Books, pills, health products, cleaning and sanitary products)
(Cosmetics)
Everything is stored well in different categories.
With my dressing table and trash can,
I separated my room and the kitchen.
I'm quite satisfied with my invisible partition.
- The invisible partition. - The invisible partition.
(The bathroom is quite spacious.)
What is that?
The previous tenant didn't do well with the humidity control.
There were quite a few places that were rusty or moldy.
The place that was moldy...
slightly came down like that.
- It must be the humidity. - Right.
It sank down a little.
Shouldn't that be fixed by the owner of the house...
before you moved in?
But when I first moved in,
I wasn't thorough enough at checking the house.
It was my first time checking a house.
This can be quite a long story,
- but I'll try to be quick. - Try to be quick.
It was my first time checking a house.
The previous tenant was still living in the house.
I was worried that I would be too rude...
if I checked the house in too much detail.
- Since it's your first time. - Right.
That was why I missed those details.
I talked to the owner about it after moving in.
The moldy parts have been fixed,
but there are some parts that are still moldy.
With the parts that can still function,
I'll have to deal with them...
- one by one. - I see.
She said so many things.
It's fascinating how...
- I understood everything. - It was easy to understand.
I understood everything.
- It was easy to understand. - I understood everything.
I remember everything she said without forgetting anything.
I'm not sure if I should ask this.
- Ask me anything. - Well,
- you've been in a lot of shows. - Right.
Couldn't you have moved into a bigger place?
That was the only place I could afford with what I had.
I wanted to live alone...
and I found a place that I could live in...
without feeling much pressure based on finances.
There's a reason why I started living alone a bit later.
I tried my best to apply for the youth housing system,
but I kept failing to get chosen.
I thought that my youth would end at that rate.
You might end up becoming middle-aged?
Right.
- She's very bright. - So I mustered up my courage...
to move out and start living alone.
It has been four months since I started living alone.
(The rookie tenant has woken up.)
(Grabbing)
(She takes out eye drops all of a sudden.)
My eyes are slightly open when I sleep.
My dry eye syndrome...
- has been getting worse. - You sleep with your eyes open?
- Yes. - It's because she has big eyes.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
(There's so much that it's pooling in her eyes.)
- She needs a lot. - Are you serious?
- It's like the Han River. - It looks like a pond.
(After making a pond, )
(she sits still for a while.)
(Tapping)
Does that work as a face mist as well?
I heard from somewhere that eye drops are good for the skin.
The ones with hyaluronic acid?
Hold on. Do you not blink when you speak?
It seems like she doesn't blink at all.
- I usually blink a lot, - Right.
But I think I'm trying to keep my eyes fixed as I'm nervous.
- I see. - Like this.
(She takes care of her skin with the eye drops as well.)
(Getting up)
What's that big thing that is hung up in the middle?
That's the rug in my house.
I had nowhere else to keep it. That's my shoe cabinet.
I opened up the cabinet and hung it up like that.
Gosh, every small space can be used for something.
Right.
What time is it?
Gosh, it's 10am.
I should hurry.
I should hurry up and eat.
(Let's eat quickly.)
(The refrigerator of the rookie tenant)
(It's simple inside with just the food that is needed.)
(There are traces of delivery food as well.)
We can see her life through the refrigerator.
Oh, yes.
(Rummaging)
(Grabbing)
(She takes out a breakfast ingredient...)
(without hesitation.)
(She rolls up her sleeves first.)
(A tuna can is opened.)
You still got rid of the oil.
(Emptying)
(After adding in tuna, sesame oil, and mayonnaise, )
(she skillfully prepares for the rice with tuna and mayo.)
It's like the house of a college student.
- Right. - Right.
The first house...
- of a college student. - Right.
(She mixes the rice while humming.)
(She takes out the essential dried laver...)
(for those who live alone.)
It's 10:07am.
(Her simple breakfast is ready.)
(Crunchy)
(Taking a big bite)
(It's a familiar, but still delicious taste.)
You can never fail with that.
- It always tastes good. - Right.
(Peeking)
(She looks at Wilson closely.)
What's this? I think there's something on you.
(She kindly gets the dust off Wilson.)
(You feel grateful, don't you?)
- Gosh, that was scary! - It's a goblin!
Gosh! I was acting cute.
(She quickly gets done with her meal.)
(Getting up)
(She washes the dishes without taking a break.)
She's really quick.
- She does everything with speed. - Right.
She's always very quick.
(What is it?)
(Picking up)
- What? - She's taking that out as well?
- I see. - Good!
- That must be done. - That part gets really dirty.
- That must be done. - Right.
(She's focusing on washing the dishes.)
(Knocking)
- Who is it? - Who is it?
Is someone here?
(Startled)
(She rushes out quickly.)
- Oh, hello. - Hello.
Sir, I have to place the rug.
I was expecting you to come at 10:30am.
I haven't placed the rug yet.
- "Sir?" - Is that so?
I'll place it quickly.
Tell me where it needs to be set up first.
Oh, right. This way.
I want to place it here.
- Like this? - Yes.
- I'll clean this up quickly. - Okay.
- I'll bring it up. - Okay.
- What is that? - What is that?
I had this dream ever since I was a kid.
"What if I had a bunk bed?"
- What? - In that house?
I had this dream ever since I was a kid.
A bed instead of a partition?
Right.
- Hold on. It's 19 square meters. - A bunk bed?
A bunk bed in a place that big?
- That will fill up the whole place. - Right.
I had a lot of things I wanted to do...
when living alone.
I'm making them happen 1 by 1.
I wanted to utilize the space of the first floor of the bunk bed.
Just like that.
- Right. - I felt I would be really happy...
by doing this.
That was why I made a big decision to purchase a bunk bed.
This should be moved first.
- I'll clean this up quickly. - Okay.
- I'll bring it up. - Okay.
(Flapping)
(She starts making urgent steps.)
What should I wear?
- Hurry. - Check out the clapping.
Here.
(She picks her clothes without delay.)
(Brushing)
Oh, no!
That will make your gums bleed. Gosh!
The installer came faster than the appointed time.
I had dried laver earlier.
- It's to keep her manners. - Right.
(She brushes her teeth at full speed to remove the dried laver.)
Gosh, she's in a hurry.
(Her extreme anxiousness cannot be hidden.)
(She starts cleaning after getting changed.)
Gosh.
(She gets things moved diligently while panting.)
She must be really diligent.
She's really quick with her actions.
- She's so fast. - She's always really fast.
(Rushing)
(Throwing)
(Her abandoned sock gets thrown into a corner.)
(There we go!)
(She moves quickly to place the rug.)
Okay.
Gosh.
- Sir. - Yes?
I moved everything.
I tried my best to pretend not to be out of breath.
"Sir."
(She crouches in the corner.)
- On top of the rug, right? - Yes.
(She's taking a breather while crouching on the floor.)
She's sitting there like a cat.
Where would you like to place the steps?
Would you like them here?
- After opening up the right side, - Right.
- this side seems better. - This way?
- Right. - This way? Got it.
Thank you.
I still haven't decided.
- Will you be using this as the mat? - Yes.
You should use a thin mat for a bunk bed.
Why is that?
- You need space for the ceiling. - Right. The ceiling.
- Right. - I see.
I should use this top bunk just for sleeping then.
You can do that.
(Chuckling)
It's exciting...
- to make your own space. - Right.
- I'm curious how it will look. - In her imagination,
- the perfect setup is already made. - Right.
(Gyeong Hye bought some coffee.)
- Have a sip of this first. - Right.
(Taking out)
- Wipe your sweat with this. - Right. Thank you.
- It got so hot, right? - Right.
- She's a bright person. - She's really bright.
- Right. - Right.
You know how it's even more confusing...
when you're familiar with it, right?
It must be tougher for you when the weather gets hotter.
- The weather... - It's still quite heavy.
It's bigger than what I expected.
It's always like this. It's my first time living alone.
You're setting up my first bunk bed...
at my first house.
- But... - It's an honor.
No. I should be honored. But...
Gosh, it's a lot more than what I expected.
Did you do that on purpose?
(You're doing fine, right?)
From afar, one might think she's a ghost living in this house.
(The ghost of small talk up close)
- An earth-bound spirit. - A ghost stuck in this house.
I was an installer of air conditioners in the past.
Those clients are the most burdensome.
- Gosh! - Really?
- Why is that? - I'm serious.
- Let me explain. - She praised him...
- and got him coffee. - Well,
giving him coffee was great.
- Giving him coffee was great, - Right.
But he might get nervous that way.
Because she's looking at him all the time.
(Staring)
That might make him feel nervous.
I'm bad at having small talks,
so I love it when people talk to me like that.
- Really? - Thank you.
- Gyeong Hye is just like me. - Right.
I keep having small talks with everyone.
Whenever we have team dinners together,
we're the only ones left after our small talks.
We talk about all sorts of things together.
- We talk endlessly. - The others get sick of it.
(The others get sick of it.)
Why would they get sick of it?
(We love small talks.)
- Bring it up. - Right.
It isn't heavy.
(The mattress is placed to finish things off.)
(Screaming)
- Oh, my gosh. She's draining me. - She's so cute.
"My dream!"
(Gyeong Hye's dream finally becomes true.)
- It's nice. - There's more space now.
- It looks cozy. - Right.
(It's nice!)
Good!
(Delighted)
It was something I dreamed of since I was a kid.
I feel like...
- I'm about to shed tears. - Right.
(Tearing up)
- It was a touching moment. - She looks emotional.
- That would make her tear up. - I dreamed of it for a while.
The thing that I dreamed of...
is placed right before my eyes.
Gosh.
I can't really grasp what kind of emotion it was,
but I felt really happy.
I hesitate to start things as I'm always full of fear.
I'm starting to feel emotional after watching the clip.
I always think so much before making a decision.
That was why it took me so long to decide to live alone.
The fact that I did something out of confidence...
You're so kind.
It didn't even touch her eyes.
(She did this.)
- Well... - I've never seen that before.
- Right. - What was that?
Well, I didn't want my makeup to get on his handkerchief.
- I'm wearing makeup today. - She's so considerate.
She's considerate with everything she does.
Thank you so much, Sung Hwan.
(A heartwarming battle of being kind)
When you move out, give the company a call...
and someone will come to help you uninstall the bed.
I wish it would be you when that time comes.
- Is that so? - Right.
- That would be great. - She's so cute.
- He won't answer the call. - Goodbye.
I would've collapsed after getting home if I were him.
- I must've been too excited. - He must feel drained.
- Gosh, it looks great. - Feeling drained?
(She feels great.)
(She dusts off her blanket with this great feeling.)
(Is she dancing?)
(Gyeong Hye gets done with her touching house renewal.)
Okay.
Here are the sheets.
Sheets? For the sink?
- I'll give it a try. - The green part?
- It's to make it look neat. - Right.
Just that part is green.
- Right. - That part does look off.
I bought them to make it match with the color on top.
I think it will look a lot better that way.
All right.
(Let's check the instructions first.)
Instructions.
Place it so that all sides can be covered.
(She positions herself in front of the target.)
All sides? Gosh!
(Gyeong Hye places the sheet.)
(Gosh!)
- Was this custom-made or what? - It fits perfectly.
- Right? - Right.
It's the perfect size.
Don't things feel great from the start?
This is fascinating. It fits perfectly.
All right. I got it.
Just remove around 10cm.
Gosh, my hands are shaking.
It must be done at once.
It rolls up so much. Hold on.
(She places the sheet gently on the side of the sink.)
- Please! - There must be no bubbles.
The top part must be applied well.
- I'm terrible with those things. - It must be a good start.
- No air should go in! - No!
(She keeps going while pressing it with her hand.)
(She's completely focusing while keeping her breath in.)
(Gosh!)
Please.
Oh, yes!
(She manages to get it stuck.)
(She rubs against it to get rid of the air.)
There you go.
(Hold on!)
Just like the screen protector.
(There's a bubble on one side.)
(There can't be any bubbles.)
- That's hard to do. - Right.
(She uses the scraper to remove the bubbles.)
I tried to apply the wallpaper on my own at home.
- There are bubbles everywhere. - You get bubbles.
- There are experts for a reason. - Right.
Right. But to call an expert,
- it was too expensive. - Right.
That's true as well.
(That was why the rookie tenant decided to do it on her own.)
- Gosh! - Gosh!
(What are we to do?)
There are bubbles.
- I should've pulled this side. - It's a huge bubble!
It should be removed.
It has to be removed to get it sorted.
(This wasn't what I wanted.)
(She urgently tries to fix it by pressing it with her hands.)
- Oh, no! - Oh, gosh!
(It's a mess.)
I hate seeing these things, Gyeong Hye.
(I hate seeing these things, Gyeong Hye.)
Gosh, Gyeong Hye!
I have to finish it off since I've started.
Let's be bold. Nice and bold.
(The result is a disaster.)
- I'm sorry. Gosh. - Oh, yes!
It's contemporary art.
(She keeps touching her work of art.)
- Gosh, it looks awful. - Gosh!
Guesthouses that are out of business have walls that look like that.
Right.
Okay. Let's quickly get it covered.
(Laughing)
You won't get it removed?
No way. You're not going to remove it?
(Gyeong Hye hurriedly covers it without removing it.)
This part can't be covered.
No. It gives off a certain vibe this way.
(This time, she removes the door to apply the sheet.)
(Will she be able to do well?)
(She rubs against it many times with the same posture.)
Gosh, it's hot.
(She finally manages to get it applied.)
(Groaning)
- This is so annoying! - Gosh!
I hate it! Gosh!
I hate these moments.
I detest these moments.
Who would like these moments?
I gave it a try, thinking that it would end quickly.
It turned out to be really hard.
I should lie down for a while.
On your knees, just for a while.
Right. You would want to lie down.
(The chaotic sheet process gets paused.)
(Gyeong Hye falls asleep soon.)
(Knocking)
(Startled)
Who is it?
Someone else has come?
You're here.
(Wailing)
Gyeong Hye!
- Chan Hyeong! - I'm here.
- Gyeong Hye! - Chan Hyeong!
It's Actor Lee Chan Hyeong.
(The one known as the new intern in "Hospital Playlist")
- He looks great. - Right.
When I first moved in,
there were many things that had to be done.
He helped me out so much with many different things.
- He's a great guy. - He's a great friend.
- Right. - He's good-looking.
Hey, Chan Hyeong. What is all this?
- I brought this for you. - What is all this?
- Side dishes. - Side dishes?
- Side dishes? My goodness. - Chan Hyeong, this is incredible.
I made them with my mom.
I can't believe you brought side dishes.
(Are you serious?)
Oh, my goodness.
I can't believe you brought side dishes.
(What's that?)
Oh, my goodness.
She is so funny.
She is like a fictional character. I can't believe that pose.
What's that? Did you make a heart with your feet?
Are you a mermaid?
(By any chance, are you a mermaid?)
I can't believe you brought side dishes.
I did my best with the side dishes.
I'm used to it...
because she has been that energetic for the past ten years.
- What? The bunk bed. - The bunk bed is here.
- Your place became spacious. - Chan Hyeong, come here.
Your place has improved a lot.
- Can I check out the side dishes? - Of course.
Chan Hyeong, if you keep making me side dishes...
- Sit down and get comfortable. - Check them out.
- Here? - Watch your head.
- This is the sitting room. - He entered for the first time.
- I know. - Yes.
Maybe it'd be too much to call you a visitor. I don't know.
- You're the first visitor. - You set up the hangers too.
Well done.
What? You should vinyl wrap his socks.
(What? You should vinyl wrap his socks.)
- You're observant. - I'm sure they'll get wrinkly.
It'll be hard not to get wrinkly.
Chan Hyeong, did your mom make these?
- My mom and I made them. - My goodness.
- I'll put them in the fridge. - Okay.
- I'll be back. - They'll last a month.
I'll put them in the fridge.
Chan Hyeong, this is the best.
I'm so thankful for your mom. I can't believe it.
I'm so thankful.
- No way. - They're so tasty.
Ask her if I can talk to her on the phone.
If she is working, I can call her later.
Mom, Gyeong Hye...
wants to thank you.
Ma'am.
Hello, Gyeong Hye.
These are the side dishes I absolutely love.
Chan Hyeong told me that he was going to your place.
- Right. - So we made them for you.
I'll enjoy them, Ma'am.
- Okay. - Thank you, Mom.
All right.
(Hopping)
(She exits cutely after finishing the call.)
I want to make something insanely tasty...
for your mom.
I have older friends...
who are seniors in terms of living alone.
They kindly give me tips...
and send me things I need. I'm so thankful.
Jun Myun sends me...
kimchi every year.
- She sends me different kinds. - Her kimchi is delicious.
So thankfully, I never run out of kimchi.
Hye Soo sends me the invigorating food items...
such as oysters and beef. I'm so thankful for that.
As for Hye Ri... I don't have much interest...
in applying makeup. I'm not very good at it.
She gives me so many makeup products.
I'm so blessed to live alone and receive everyone's help.
Today, I went to Hye Ri's place...
and borrowed her clothes to look cool on the show.
- Really? - Yes.
- Are those Hye Ri's items? - My friend let me borrow...
this jacket and watch.
My eyes kept wandering to that watch. It's Hye Ri's.
- You have so many good friends. - I know.
- It's like that... - I'm so blessed.
- She must be a good friend as well. - Everyone loves Gyeong Hye.
She shows consideration in small ways.
Her seniors receive so much energy from her.
I find myself contacting her without even realizing it.
- "How are you these days?" - I think I understand.
She has so much energy.
- That's right. - She is positive.
- Ji Hyeon's energy is drained. - My goodness.
(Nodding)
I actually saw him before filming.
- Where? - You're right.
You visited the waiting rooms.
No. I saw you at the salon.
- What? - I didn't go to the salon today.
- Your photo was at the salon. - I see.
- You know, I... - Listen.
- I bet... - Then say that you saw a photo.
- Don't say that you saw him. - I bet she talked...
to that photo for 15 minutes.
Seriously.
(Chuckling)
You're very nice.
Ji Hyeon, you looked very cheerful when I first saw you today.
- Now, you look tired. - It isn't like that.
(Compared to the beginning, he has lost a lot of energy.)
I'll be calm.
- She is charming. - She is charming indeed.
Gyeong Hye, did you do this by yourself?
Yes. It shows that I've done it by myself, right?
- It's much harder than it looks. - Really?
Yes. I thought I'd be able to do it easily.
- I actually hid this side. - Okay.
This side is worse.
- This side? - Right?
- I see it. - Look at the bottom.
- There are many air bubbles. - Yes.
It's like the moon.
It can't be helped.
I won't get hurt even if I bump into it.
You had that in mind when you added the air bubbles, right?
I didn't have that in mind. It was a lucky coincidence.
In any case, there are air bubbles.
- This is the charm of living alone. - You're right.
I think I've had enough of that charm.
From now on...
- Do you want to do well? - Yes.
Okay.
- Let's give it a go. - Effort will get us anywhere.
I love the spirit.
Chan Hyeong, it's very straight.
(He scissors without hesitation.)
- Let's see. - He is good.
Chan Hyeong does it so calmly.
- Let's give it a go. - Okay. Let's give it a go.
- Here? - Yes.
There you go.
Like this?
Yes. Push it down.
That's good. Chan Hyeong, that's good.
Chan Hyeong, that's great.
- My goodness. - He is good.
- He is very calm. - I know.
- Okay. - Chan Hyeong, this is a good start.
- Hold this part. - What should I do? This part?
- Pull it down gently as I go. - Gently.
That's right. She needs to hold the bottom part.
(The wrap goes on cleanly.)
He is like a professional.
The DIYers I saw...
- in the videos were like that. - You're right.
- This is therapeutic. - It isn't easy to do that.
I know. He was so good at it.
- Like this. - Chan Hyeong, I totally...
feel like I have a professional in the house.
It looks like it's the original color.
It looks so neat.
(Neat)
He did a great job.
- Ta-da. - Shall I open it now?
- Hold on. - We need to wrap this part too.
- I'll push it in with a knife. - Exactly.
Okay. Let me do the small tasks like that.
- Okay. - Okay?
- I'm bad at such tasks. - You do the big tasks.
I'll be in charge of such tasks.
(They take off the wrap with many bubbles.)
Hurry up and take it off.
All right.
(He applies the vinyl wrap cleanly.)
(It's complete.)
(They finish vinyl wrapping the bottom cabinet.)
It's so cool.
No way.
It looks so clean.
It looks new.
- The trick was working calmly. - That's right.
Chan Hyeong, I'm sorry, but a bigger task remains.
Let me tell you what it is.
- It's the bathroom door. - Okay.
If you look here...
Please help me with the doorknob...
- and hinges. - Okay.
You want to switch the hinges.
The hinges were rusty,
so I was worried that the door would collapse.
- That was why I asked for help. - Hinges need to be secure.
That's right. And opening the door from the inside after lockup...
got harder because of the rust. Usually, the door opens smoothly.
- But my door didn't do that. - It didn't do that.
- I couldn't use it. - You needed to switch it.
It could be dangerous.
I was dangerous when I really needed to use the restroom,
personally speaking.
You bought many things.
- Me? - Yes.
I hope it works.
- You didn't hear it, right? - Right.
(He figures out the problem and begins to fix it.)
- I'll take off the door first. - Is it off already?
- Yes. - He does everything with ease.
I know. He does everything without a fuss.
He is incredible.
It's all done. Chan Hyeong, I'll open it from the outside.
- From the outside. - Okay.
- I'll open the door. - Okay.
- Shall I open the door? - Okay.
- Okay. I'll lock it. - Hi.
Okay. Lock it.
It's locked.
- Okay. - You could unlock it, right?
- Yes. - Hold on.
I couldn't open it before.
- I can open it now. - Okay.
(Oh, my)
The doorknob is complete.
Chan Hyeong, I made you work too much.
It's okay.
Thanks to you, I'll be able to shower with the door closed.
I had to shower with the door wide open before.
Really? You were afraid that the door would get locked.
- I see. - It was cold in winter.
It's dangerous when the door gets locked.
- Chan Hyeong. - Yes?
(Taking out)
It's nothing.
- What is it? - You work out.
- What is it? - People who work out...
- tend to prefer this brand. - Is it a present?
- Yes. - The people who work out...
I don't know if it's your style.
- What's this, Gyeong Hye? - It's nothing.
- You didn't have to. - It's nothing.
- My goodness. - It's nothing.
You always help me.
You helped me with the curtains last time.
I hope it looks good on you.
- Please hand it over to me. - Okay.
Chan Hyeong, you made it possible for me to shower...
- with the door closed. Thank you. - Thank you.
The two of them get along.
Thank you.
I'll get going, Gyeong Hye. Thanks for the clothes.
Don't mention it. You've done more for me.
- I'll get going. - I'll fill those containers later.
- Okay. - You know what I mean.
- Thank you so much. - Seriously, they're like a family.
- I know. - I'll get going.
- I'm so thankful for him. - Leave it. I'll throw it out later.
- Bye. - He is like her younger brother.
- Thank you so much. - I thought they were related.
- Bye. - Bye.
(She hurriedly sends off the younger friend she is close to.)
(Hurried)
I need to hurry up and head out.
- She'll finally go out. - Yes.
(She washes up and changes into a new outfit.)
She looks like a model.
Let's put on the glasses.
All done.
(She dresses up and hurriedly heads out.)
I'll clean the house after I come back.
(She goes somewhere in a car.)
Oh, no!
(Covering their mouths)
(Dancing)
(Flipping her hair)
(Did you really not know that we were seeing each other?)
Oh, my goodness.
Gosh, Gyeong Hye.
You're always like that.
- Sung Hwan. - You're always like that.
(As she drove on while singing on top of her lungs, )
(she's arrived somewhere.)
(Running)
Youn Sang Hyun.
Where is she?
Where is that?
- Sang Hyun. - Yes.
- Did you eat? - No, not yet.
- Was it busy? - No.
- It wasn't too busy? - No.
What? You own a cafe?
Check if there are any drinks we're out of.
Wash the fruit container and change the paper towels too.
It's been two years since I started doing the part-time job.
- Oh, you do a part-time job? - Yes.
When there aren't any projects,
we don't have a fixed income.
I thought it'd be nice if there was a chance for me to earn money.
And I got to do a part-time job here.
That's how I started doing it.
For real?
I worked at a cafe as a part-time job for five years.
But what do you do when you have a project to work on?
Oh, I'm currently working on two projects.
Actually, there are many actors...
who work as a part-timer at the cafe.
- So you help each other. - So we... Yes.
- You take turns helping each other. - That's right.
That's nice.
I went in for an audition in the morning.
He's Actor Youn Sang Hyun...
who starred in "Under the Queen's Umbrella."
Oh, they're all actors.
Can I wash my hands for a second?
(She washes her hands as soon as she comes in.)
The afternoon group...
checks the menu that ran out in advance.
Sang Hyun, you're the best. It's really clean.
After the morning sales,
the floor could've gotten dirty.
You work so hard.
I think we're done, Gyeong Hye.
(Quickly getting ready for the afternoon sales)
Welcome.
(The first customers of the afternoon sales enter.)
I'll help with your order here.
Can you make the cream latte warm?
Yes, I can make the cream latte warm.
- I'll have it warm. - You want it warm?
The two menus are 12.5 dollars. I'll help you with the payment.
Welcome.
Thank you. I'll have it ready right away.
Hello.
I'll take two Americanos and...
Can I have the milk tea cold?
Yes, of course.
We have a 30-percent discount for drinks to go,
so the total is 9.31 dollars.
- This is the milk tea... - A latte...
Right. The latte and milk tea.
It could take a bit because we have an order to go.
Thank you. I'll bring the drinks to your table.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
She's so bright. It's so nice.
(Drinks order: 2 Americanos, cream latte, matcha latte...)
- There are many different menus, - They ordered a lot.
So it must not be easy.
Yes, there are many different menus.
(But with quick hands, )
(she makes a cream latte in no time.)
(Arranging cups in perfect rows and columns)
Gosh, look how fast her hands are.
She's so reliable.
- She's really fast. - She's really quick.
(Sang Hyun makes coffee smoothly.)
A word will spread that only good-looking ones are there.
- I know. - That's right. It's so romantic.
It's totally "Coffee Prince."
- You're right. - You're right.
It's a really pleasant working environment.
- I'm envious. - It is romantic.
It's a scene straight out of a comic book.
(She makes a coffee carrier in no time.)
Look how fast she makes that.
Look at her folding that.
(She quickly makes a carrier.)
(Then she thoroughly writes the name of the drink.)
- The owner must feel... - I know.
Really reassured to have a part-timer like her.
I know.
(Here's the coffee you ordered.)
Here's your cream latte. Enjoy.
This is milk tea, and this is the decaf vanilla latte.
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
Excuse me. Here's your order to go.
Are you the actor I know?
- Many people must recognize her. - That's right.
- Thank you. - Thank you. It's an honor.
No, I'm grateful.
(Holding hands tight)
Bye. Come again.
Actually, I run into my fans by chance,
and they greet me so brightly. I'm really grateful for that.
- It's really nice. - So I...
I get so much energy from them.
They compliment me a lot too.
- Bye. - There are so many people...
in that area.
(Taking something)
(Thump)
(Shaking with all her strength)
My gosh!
- It's become a bar in earnest. - A bar.
Yes, at night, we sell alcoholic drinks too.
The mood must be really nice at night.
You should go there on the weekend.
Hello! "Thump!"
(Hello!)
Hyun Moo, go there and balance things out.
- Why? - It's too hip.
Joy, Hyun Moo will go there.
Yes. I'll go when you go. "Welcome, Joy."
- Joy. - "You came so late."
- That's so terrible. - And I'll be serving that day.
- And he will... - I'll be serving.
- "Joy, you're here!" - Hello.
- People would think we got busy. - It's so nice.
(Welcome to Pepper Prince, branch number 1.)
(Taking quick steps)
Excuse me. Where can I put Peach Crush?
Here you go. Enjoy.
Excuse me.
I'll get your other drink right away.
Excuse me. Where can I put Cinderella?
She must be physically drained, but she's always smiling.
Normally, if there are many people like that,
staff members don't serve drinks.
But she's serving the drinks herself.
(Amazed)
(Time goes fast without a chance for her to sit down.)
(It's already late at night.)
Thank you. Good night.
I'll help with your payment.
- Thank you. Good night. - Good night.
(The last customer leaves.)
(She quickly starts the closing shift.)
She really lives her day to the fullest.
(She finishes the remaining dishes.)
(Thoroughly doing the recycling separation)
(Rushing)
There are times when I find it hard while doing the part-time job,
but I think earning money...
can't be easy.
But I earn money to spend it on me.
I think it's a good thing that there's a place...
where I can earn money...
- and adjust my schedule. - Good night.
(She's just grateful.)
Let's go.
- Great job. - Great job.
They finished it up perfectly.
- Let's go. - Let's get it.
- Bye. I'm leaving. - You did great. Bye.
Bye!
(It's already 11:30pm.)
(Before the day ends, )
(she hurries home.)
Looking back, on my way home on a bus...
after doing a part-time job,
- I became sentimental. - Right.
- I always felt that way. - Right. You feel strange.
That's right.
(She arrives home close to midnight.)
(Exclaiming)
It looks really cozy.
And you're sleeping in it for the first time.
- Yes! - It's your first sleep.
It looks really cozy after seeing you work.
- That's right. - That's right.
It looks different from earlier.
(Yawning)
I should get changed.
(Gyeong Hye comes out after getting changed.)
(She heads straight to the kitchen.)
Since I'm starved...
I couldn't have a proper meal.
You need to eat before you sleep since you'd be hungry.
- You can't fall asleep too. - Have something delicious.
(Opening)
(Smiling)
(Becoming lively again after seeing food)
That's right. The side dishes Chan Hyeong gave.
Gosh, it's full.
- I'm so excited. - I was so happy...
to have the side dishes from his mom.
- You look really happy. - Gosh!
You're putting them in a separate dish.
I didn't want them to go bad when she made them for me.
I wanted to keep them well and have them for a long time.
Gyeong Hye is really neat.
It's troublesome to put the side dishes in a separate dish...
after working.
(Turning on the lights for the mood)
Thank you for the food.
(A meal filled with the homemade dishes is ready.)
(Taking a bite of the cockle first)
This is crazy.
- Gosh. - Seriously... Gosh.
(Exclaiming)
Gosh.
It's something you can't eat often...
- because it takes a lot of work. - That's right.
(Crunchy)
I feel like I'm eating it after work.
It was so good.
When you get home after work,
out of a need to compensate for your hard work...
You tend to eat more.
I'd turn on the delivery app right away.
(It's even more delicious because she worked hard.)
As for living alone,
it has clear pros and cons.
One of the pros is that...
you can focus on yourself solely...
because you're by yourself in that space.
"What should I eat today?"
"I find that uncomfortable."
It keeps coming back to me.
But when you live with family,
it becomes, "What should we have for dinner today?"
The con is that when it comes to something you haven't tried,
you could get flustered a lot or feel discouraged.
But if the pro can beat the con...
even by one percent,
it's worth a try.
It's a time when you get to learn about yourself.
(I'm Learning About Myself)
Thank you for the video.
- Thank you. - You're an energizer.
I feel like I watched a movie titled, "Park Gyeong Hye."
There was a movie called "Bridget Jones's Diary."
- Yes! - That's right!
She's really lovely.
It was like watching "Park Gyeong Hye's Diary."
- Thank you. - It was so much fun.
You know, there are friends like this.
The friends who turn my day into a movie.
- Yes, there are. - My day...
could've been dull and boring,
but it becomes dazzling thanks to this friend.
Right.
So I wanted to become close to her.
I'd love that. I like you so much.
(So I wanted to become close to her.)
Gyeong Hye, what are your plans going forward?
I'm going to wrap up the project I'm working on well.
There is still a lot of stuff to do.
There are still many things I need to take care of.
I'll take care of them 1 by 1,
and I'll fill my daily life well.
That's great.
We'll root for Gyeong Hye's single life full of energy...
- and positivity. - Thank you!
Thank you.
(Next story)
(The reliable and cheerful aide in "Perfect Crown")
(The scene-stealer with crazy presence...)
(in "Weak Hero Class 2" and "Crash Landing on You")
(It's been 6 years since he started living alone.)
(Actor Yu Su Bin)
(Laughing)
(I tend to be a little lazy.)
(He spends ages lying in bed.)
(He finally gets up.)
(Where he headed...)
(was none other than just in front.)
(An optimized route designed by his laziness)
(The closer, the better.)
(Boiling)
(He boils water in a pot for coffee.)
(I'm even too lazy to cut an apple.)
(He waters plants with drinking water.)
(Gosh, I'm so lazy.)
(It's nice to see you.)
(The friends he's glad to see are Actress Lee Yeon...)
(and IU.)
(They're so close that they see each other every week.)
(Peekaboo)
(He's not lazy to see his friends.)
(He always...)
(Exuding sweetness effortlessly)
(When prompted, )
(he shows a special skill.)
(Impressed)
(Sweet selective laziness)
(Perfect Lazy Boy)
(The cross-country walk...)
(continues.)
(A heavy downpour)
My head is spinning.
(Dizzy)
(It doesn't end no matter how much we walk.)
(How come we can't see the ocean once?)
(The closer they get to Gwangalli, the more painful it gets.)
(Steps taken precariously)
(He can't breathe.)
(Actually, I was done back then.)
(The reason he didn't stop despite that)
(A promise with his precious friend)
(Whenever he had it hard, he thought of his friend...)
(and took each step.)
(While doing the cross-country walk, )
(I kept walking with her.)
(The record of the last moment of his cross-country walk)
(See you later.)
(Now I can call your name.)
(My Forever Rosy Path)